[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "What do we think we know and what don't we know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Well, Piers, this is very serious business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "LOCATION": ["South Koreans"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "WP", "POS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "What's been the reaction to this there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Well, it's disturbing because we're talking about delivery of these weapons, Piers, and that's really been what's at issue here for South Koreans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "How did that happen and why did it happen like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "ORGAN: General Clark, how worried should we be, you think, right now about what's happening in North Korea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, I think there's always a chance that you could have a spark, an accident, a miscalculation, an overzealous commander on one side or the other that starts something that neither side can really stop easily and gets out of control.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clark"], "LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Governor Richardson, I mean, should the Chinese be taking a more direct role now in trying to calm things down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "I don't believe the Chinese are doing as much as they could and they're sending mixed messages.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Richardson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "I mean, are they supportive of their people when this kind of thing happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Well, I mean, you think that here is this incredibly totalitarian and brutal country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "My question is about North Korea and I just wanted to know since you've been there, what is daily life there like and what do they think about America and Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "EX", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "EX", "IN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Megan"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Nick, what is daily life like in North Korea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Well, I mean, a lot of it, of course, is hunt for food, for things like this, and -- but the thing that really struck me the most, Megan, when I kind of randomly walked into homes and there's always a bit of a stir, this American, you know, wanting to see a home.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Did you find it soothing or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "I sure --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Did you sense an extreme anti-Americanism?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "No, I really don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Nuclear Nonproliferation Treaty"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Tell me about that and tell me, is it always the same, is it always the same pattern?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, I can say they broke out of the Nuclear Nonproliferation Treaty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "What do you think is going to happen in the next few weeks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "My best guess is that North Korea is throwing a tantrum, it's trying to get international attention.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Americans don't traditionally do a lot of traveling, do they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNPS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Relative to a lot of other first world countries, we are low on passport holders and we don't travel as much as I think we should.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Why is it, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "So I'm actually wondering if you have some practical tips for somebody who is looking to go ahead and take the leap and go abroad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, look, I'm all for going even deeper into debt for a travel experience and great meals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "You think it's worth that for a show about food, essentially?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "I'm having fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "I want to know what do other countries think about American food and when they think, what do you think comes to their mind, burgers, fries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Preparing one meal to personify America, what would you cook?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Really, I make a great hamburger.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "But if you did know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "He puts those on his breakfast cereal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 409, "question": "Frog?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 410, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Jellyfish?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Nope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What do you think it is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "OURDAIN: I don't care.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "This is balut isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Are you allowed to serve that in New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "There is a very hot hipster restaurant currently in New York where hipsters with ironic facial hair and sunglasses are lined up 12 deep to get in and eat this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tony"]}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Where's Tanya?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Hi, Tony.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tanya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "My question is during all your travels all over the world, sampling food there, and some are your hosts, how do you react while you're on camera and you don't like something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "Look, the only times -- I try -- number one rule on the show is try to be a good guest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "What do you think should be done about guns in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well, I just think all weapons should be absolutely outlawed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130411pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "We have an overwhelming majority in this country that support common sense laws that keep America safe and we just started going where is everybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Tell me exactly how this works.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}]